Behold the sweetfish river running through my beloved hometown.
You who seek the Golden Land, follow its path downstream in search of the key.
As you travel down it, you will see a village.
In that village, look for the shore the two will tell you of.
There sleeps the key to the Golden Land.
The one who obtains the key must then travel to the Golden Land in accordance with these rules.
On the first twilight, offer the six chosen by the key as sacrifices.
On the second twilight, those who remain shall tear apart the two who are close.
On the third twilight, those who remain shall praise my noble name.
On the fourth twilight, gouge the head and kill.
On the fifth twilight, gouge the chest and kill.
On the sixth twilight, gouge the stomach and kill.
On the seventh twilight, gouge the knee and kill.
On the eighth twilight, gouge the leg and kill.
On the ninth twilight, the witch shall revive, and none shall be left alive.
On the tenth twilight, at journey's end, you shall attain to the power of the Golden Land's treasures, once and for the last time.
The witch shall praise the wise and bestow four treasures.
One,
shall be all the gold from the Golden Land.
shall be the resurrection of all the dead souls.
One,
shall be the resurrection of the love that was lost.
One...
...shall be to put the witch to sleep for all time.
Sleep peacefully,
my beloved witch...
Beatrice!!
Look, George-sama! They're so cute, look, look!
It's so cute. Look at it!
Yeah, they're really cute. I almost want to eat them.
I, I'd feel so sorry for them...
Is that so? But that's what I think.
Uh...
I-it's so awesome. It's such a big tank! It's like they sliced off a part of the sea and brought it here.
Interesting description. A slice of the sea.
Indeed, this may not be the real sea.
But, as long as they swim here and they believe that this is the sea, then to them it certainly is the beautiful sea.
Somehow, I feel so happy, it makes me scared.
I didn't expect this to happen either.
I've thought of how nice it would be if it turned out like this.
I heard that the power of thought is imbued with magic.
Yes, I think that's magic for sure.
But that's not quite right.
Eh?
Every time we meet, you keep becoming more and more beautiful,
and you have grown to be that much more important to me as well.
If the same thing happened to you, then the fact that we are here today is simply an inevitable consequence,
not some magic or miracle.
George-sama,
Oh, that's right. I have one more whim, but I'm not sure if you'd be willing to listen.
What is it, George-sama?
Could you stop calling me "George-sama"? At least when it's just the two of us.
Let's create that as a rule.
A-a rule?
Ok. ...George-san.
Yeah, that sounds wonderful. I'm so happy, Shannon.
I have the name Sayo as well...
I see. Then, I'll call you Sayo from now on.
Alright, Sayo?
Yes.
It truly is a deep blue sea.
I'm so happy to see this sea with you, Sayo.
Me too, George-san.
This sea and the sky are all so blue.
Yes, if you can look at it with two people,
then it really is real magic.
With this mirror...
Go and taste the fruits of that wisdom.
But, this is the only thing I can do when I am trapped on Rokkenjima.
Free me from life as furniture!
I'll accept new sufferings, and become human!
Break the eternally unchangeable fate that imprisons me,
into pieces!!
I kept my promise, now it's your turn!
Please,
I want you to fulfill my wish,
Beatrice-sama!!
Il giudizio finale
The final judgement
Sta per essere emesso
Is about to be delivered
Nessuno può emendarsi
No one can amend
Dal peccato che
The sin that flows
Scorre nelle vene
Within their veins
Uminari no shirabe ni
The dark clouds flock
Kurokumo wa sora e tsudou
To the tune of the rumbling sea
Arashi wo yobu kaze wa
The winds summon the tempest
Takaraka ni
As they thunderously resonate
Nazomeku kotonoha ni
The witches chuckle meaningfully
Majotachi wa fukumiwarau
At the cryptic medleys of words
Ibitsu na yoru no utage wa
As this twisted banquet at night
Kurikaesu
Keeps repeating itself
Ah,
(Sperare)
(To hope)
Naraku e to ochita
Towards hell they fell;
(è peccato?)
(Is it a sin?)
Kiniro no chou wa
These golden butterflies—
Ikutsu no tsumi ni
Just how many sins
Hane wo nurashite yuku no?
Will they soak their wings in?
Nakanaide torawareta
Don't cry... break through
Gensou wo kowashi
This illusion entrapping you
Ichidokiri no
And let us rise above
Shuuen wo ageyou
This demise one last time
Hatasenai yakusoku wa
The promises unfulfilled
Mune no oku kogetsuite
Sear deep within my chest
Akaku akaku hazeteku yo
As they keep splitting open in red, ever so red—
Nee...
Please...
Tu sei senza peccato?
Are you without sin?
(Nee...)
(Please...)
Quanto sarà pesante
How heavy will
Il mio castigo?
My punishment be?
(Mio mio castigo)
(My punishment)
Ti accorgi delle
Do you notice
Voci senza voce?
The voiceless voices?
Ti accorgi delle voci senza voce?
Do you notice the voiceless voices?
Ti accorgi dei tuoi peccati
Do you notice your own sins?
Ienai kizuguchi wa
These wounds which won't heal
Kurenai no bara no you ni
Are just like a crimson rose
Nikushimi yadoru
Amidst the hatred that dwells
Kokoro ni hana hiraku
In my heart—they begin to bloom
Ah,
(Serbare il segreto)
(To keep the secret)
Tsubasa ubawareta
Robbed of its wing;
(è peccato?)
(is it a sin?)
Katahane no tori wa
This one-winged bird—
Saigo no toki ni
In its last moments
Dare no namae wo yobu no?
Whose name will it call for?
Nakanaide torawareta
Don't cry... break through
Gensou wo kowashi
This illusion entrapping you
Ichidokiri no
And let us rise above
Shuuen wo ageyou
This demise one last time
Hatasenai yakusoku wa
The promises unfulfilled
Mune no oku kogetsuite
Sear deep within my chest
Akaku akaku hazeteku yo
As they keep splitting open in red, ever so red—
Nee...
Please...
(Nee...)
(Please...)
Impossibile arrivare
It is impossible to arrive
Al vero segreto se non ci
At the truth of the secret if
Si accorge di tutto l’amore
One fails to realize all the love
Today, Ushiromiya Eva, Hideyoshi and George are coming to visit.
Do not neglect your duties.
Yes.
At that time, I was a middle school student, and sometimes I dreamt of love like children my age.
But really, I should not dream like that,
because I am furniture.
Hoh, that does sound promising. Study a lot at your father's, and do your best to become able to help him soon.
Yes, thank you so much.
It's not language or math you learn in school. What you study is the attitude to have towards studying.
Stop it, dear. George is always giving it his all. Right?
Truly excellent. I wish our Jessica would learn from him...
Ughhh. Are you still holding a grudge about that test score？
Jessica, shouldn't you learn to be a bit more gracious with your speech, not to speak of your studies?
Later, I will speak to you at length about your language.
If the little child here is bothering you, just say so.
Excuse me.
Ah- Milady!
Shannon, the tea is getting cold. Serve it quickly.
Yes.
I... I ruined the peaceful atmosphere here before.
My heart is pounding, I can't afford to make mistakes.
Stop, please...
This tea smells good. Is it Earl Grey tea?
Hoh, George-kun, you know a lot about black tea?
Someone who helped me once explained to me that there used to be an Earl of Grey in England, and this tea was named after him.
With that knowledge, the tea seems to get taster.
Does it not? Shannon, thank you for the delicious black tea.
Ah, no.
George nii-san could always easily change the topic at a time like this.
When I think back on it, I feel that maybe this wasn't the first time he has helped me like that.
He's really good at reading between the lines in those kinds of situations. That guy's a show-off in weird ways.
Th, that's not true... I think he is a really wonderful person.
Hmmmm? Shannon...
you haven't fallen in love with George nii-san, have you?
I, umm...
What are you guys having so much fun talking about?
Ah, speaking of...
Grandfather finally came down. Now they're having an adult discussion.
Escaping then was the right choice.
Grandfather must think of us as the angel of death.
After all, this is not a family meeting - it is a meeting to borrow money for business.
My family's pretty stingy, why don't they just lend out the money?
...But, I really wish I could watch from the corner and learn.
Nii-san.
Even so, the flowers in this garden are truly splendid this year.
Ah, the atmosphere has changed again.
Why didn't I realize it before?
Um... George-sama...
Hm?
Thank you for your concern back there.
What's this?
I don't remember doing anything I should be thanked for.
My heart can't stop beating...
Speaking of, George nii-san, shouldn't you have a girlfriend by now?
Wh- what is this, all of a sudden?
Although you're pretty good at academics, I guess you don't understand at all in that regard.
Excuse me!
Ah! If George nii-san is up to it, why not practice going on a date with Shannon for a day?
Ehh?!
Th- th- that's a very appealing plan, but... I'd feel bad for Shannon-chan!
It- it's okay, I'm j-j-just a servant!
You both reacted so much!
Jessica-chan!
George.
Mother.
I've been calling you for a while.
Sor...sorry.
How rude of me, Eva-sama!
Your father and the rest have finished talking.
We're going to talk to Grandfather about you, so come on.
It couldn't be about...
Yes, a marriage meeting.
Shouldn't marriage meetings be done at a more mature age...?
Of course, we have no desire to rush.
Marriage isn't something you do after you start liking someone.
It's about getting married and then getting used to it.
You're the only son I'm proud of. We'll introduce you to someone who is a fitting partner for you.
But...
So, let's go. We're keeping Father waiting. Hurry to the mansion.
Okay.
Sorry, you two. See you later.
Then Auntie will leave too. I'm so sorry I interrupted your pleasant conversation.
No, no, please don't worry about it.
Jessica-chan, I'm sure you'll meet a wonderful person suitable for you.
Yeah, okay.
And of course, you too, Shannon-chan.
Yes! Thank you very much...
Have you really forgotten to be grateful for your schooling? Know your place.
Eh?
George may be the one who will bear the burden of the Ushiromiya family someday in the future.
Did you really think you could snatch George away, you uneducated, incompetent, unqualified, uncultured servant?
I... I didn't mean...
It's okay! You can definitely find someone who matches you as a servant.
Right?
Shannon...
I had forgotten. I am furniture.
I should be grateful for even being treated like a human.
I cannot ask for more.
Shannon.
Madam!
The head and my husband will return very soon. Has the study and staircase's cleaning been completed?
I'm very sorry, I wanted to clean it properly, so it's taken some time....
Then please clean it carefully to your heart's content.
I order you to clean the reception hall thoroughly. Until you finish that, you will not be permitted any food or rest.
How stupid I am...
I'm still dreaming that George-sama can help me here.
Nee-san is still as clumsy as always.
Kanon-kun...
Madam has been in a bad mood since this morning. You could have held your head down in silence.
Right.
People like that can go to hell!
Kanon-kun.
Cleaning the reception hall will be tough. I'll help too.
Thank you, but if Kanon-kun is punished too, I will be sad.
Just saying that you'll help is enough for me.
I understood. Do your best, Nee-san.
I will.
Please listen to my foolish words, Beatrice-sama.
I am incompetent and uneducated furniture, so I am not qualified for love.
But, if that's the case, then why was I given a heart that can know love?
If it's going to be this hard and painful, I wish I'd never been given this heart!
I see. Giving a heart to furniture, what an amusing thing to do.
Eh?
Humans have been continually searching for the elements that make up the world since before the Christian Era.
However, a single man appeared, guided by a star,
and finally explained the single true element that makes up the world.
Do you know what it is?
It is love.
Beatrice-sama...
Indeed. I am Beatrice.
I cannot believe this.
Even after thousands of years, the first expression that humans show when they see the me remains the same.
Your worries are due to love. Adam and Eve learned love. They were kicked out of paradise, and they became human.
Now that you have known love, you are no longer furniture. You are now "human".
...Umm...
It has been a long time since I have spoken with a human. I shall apologize for my talkativeness.
Although it is not a suitable apology, I will grant that desire of yours with my power.
Huh?
I am offering to bring you and the one you love together.
Re...Really?
But, I have a request.
Request?
You should know that there are small torii and shrine built on the reef close to this island.
I want you to break the mirror kept inside that shrine.
If you take action and break that mirror for me, as a reward, I will grant you your wish.
My wishes...
I'm in a very good mood today.
If you want, you may change your wish, and I can give you all of the gold I bestowed upon Kinzo.
Allow me to decline.
What?
If there's a reason, let me hear it.
I don't know why, but to this day, the island has been in peace, and nothing has happened.
So, even if I don't break the mirror, this peace should continue into the future.
I see. So that's how it is. As you said, I can make an absolute guarantee about this.
The same unbreakable days that have passed until today will continue into tomorrow, and the day after.
Forever and ever.
Please stop saying that.
You know this well.
Even imagining that you and Ushiromiya George could be joined is sinful, and foolish, foolish, foolish.
Please stop!
Foolish, foolish, know your place!
Shut up! Who the hell are you?
I apologize for being a bit too harsh.
But the promise just now will remain.
If you need my power, you can summon me at any time.
Disappear, and don't ever show yourself in front of Shannon again!
...In parting, I shall leave a single souvenir.
Nee-san!
This is...
A butterfly brooch.
Think about it, Shannon.
You are free to decide your future of your own free will.
Goodbye, furniture!
Nee-san...
Then, I fulfilled my promise with the witch in order to make my wish come true.
Beatrice-sama!
Eeeh!? A young couple going on an overnight trip and you didn't even kiss?
We're dating, but we're not married yet.
Things like that have to be done after you've sworn an oath before God.
Aah,
I want a boyfriend toooo!! I can't believe Shannon got ahead of me!
Milady is a wonderful person, so I'm sure a wonderful person will appear very soon.
Don't try to console me!
You traitor, get out!
Shannon, tell me the truth.
Okay.
Is my hair or something weird?
Is it the way I talk after all?
Milady is already a wonderful person.
But, I'm the only one who can't get a boyfriend. All my friends have boyfriends.
Everyone said that this cultural festival, they'll bring their boyfriends.
I was so sure I'd have a boyfriend before then,
but I can't find a boyfriend. Only me...
Milady...
I'm sorry for sobbing.
Shannon, it's about time, right?
But—
If you don't go quickly, Genji-san and Mom will get mad. Hurry, I'm fine!
I also... want to fall...in love.
Shannon. How long have you been watering the garden?
I- I am very sorry, Madam.
It's still the same.
That voice...
Ah!
What is it?
N-nothing.
I can't believe it... I don't see any progress since last I checked-
Please don't!
Really? You don't want to hear my reprimand?
No, that's not...
Then I won't say more. You will finish all your work by the end of today. Okay?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. That prank went a little too far.
Beatrice-sama!
Haven't seen you for a long time. What happened after?
Y- yes. Thanks to you, it's going smoothly.
Naturally, my magic is instantaneous.
Do forgive me. More importantly, I heard, I heard! About your trip alone with him.
I'm sure it was quite fun.
Yeees!
Oh! Th... that's right. Umm, Beatrice-sama. I bought some sweets as a souvenir from the trip.
Oh? A souvenir for a witch?
What interesting refreshments, thank you for the hospitality.
Next time, I shall treat you to a taste of Nero's Dolce Vita.
Um, that's alright. This is enough for me, so I'll give it back to you.
But this is yours already.
If you can treasure this as proof of our friendship, that would comfort me a bit.
If you wish to, you can also gift it to someone suffering in love.
A gift for me?
Um, by the way, can I ask you a question?
Why can some people see Beatrice-sama, but others can't?
Everyone has something that resembles a wavelength, and it makes a big difference whether or not you can perceive between witches and human.
Then... what about the Master?
Kinzo is the same. There is no one with a more pitiful lack of magical talent.
Eh?
He kept studying by himself like mad, and reached the level of magician.
And then, the Master summoned Beatrice-sama with the power of magic.
It was really just my luck.
What does that mean?
Since he was so full of enthusiasm, I generously responded and gave him a mountain of gold.
Then the Master... used that gold and succeeded in business, and grew his wealth into what it is today.
Yes, and then after obtaining every dream that could be obtained in the human world,
he began to seek the single element that makes up the world.
And then?
And thanks to that, I'm in this state.
I've been sewn in place on this island for several decades now, invisible for all this time.
Until you helped me smash that mirror.
What exactly is that mirror?
Long ago, it seems various things happened on the islands around this area.
Because of that, bad things gathered, drawn towards an evil distortion.
It seems that a traveling eastern magician or something built a shrine for the repose of souls and sealed them in there.
I was not its target. But it was a divine mirror. As a result, my power was sealed away.
The clouds have come out.
When the ocean loses its splendor, it's just a grey puddle.
You think so? I think the ocean is a beautiful deep blue, even if it gets cloudy.
These have been some unusual snacks. Now, it's almost time for you to get back to work.
After all, someone doesn't like it when you drink tea with me, right?
Kanon-kun!
It was fun, Shannon. Tell me more about George at our next tea party.
My magical power is still quite lacking. It's tiring even to show myself.
If you're that tired, never appear again.
So goodbye.
Nee-san, didn't I tell you that you shouldn't hang around with her?
Beatrice-sama isn't that bad of a person.
She's not human,
and neither are we.
We are furniture.
I am not... furniture.
We are furniture! We are less than human.
Nee-san, you're acting like you've forgotten that.
Kanon-kun...
From the beginning, we have been unqualified to love or be loved.
Nee-san, you've just been tempted by that witch, and mistakenly believe that you became human!
Kanon-kun!
Listen to me.
It is true that we are inferior to human beings.
But if we could replace that unfulfilled part... wouldn't that mean that we could become human?
That couldn't happen.
Well, look.
The sea. Kanon-kun, what color does the sea look to you?
It's a vague, dark-gray color.
It looks deep blue to me.
If I understand, and you do not, that's what it means.
I... don't understand.
Kanon-kun. Would you stick out your hand?
This is... hers...?
No, this is mine. So think of it as me and treat it with respect, okay?
But...
This charm holds true magical power.
I'm sure that it will teach you an important emotion, Kanon-kun.
The sea full of the world's first element would be a very deep blue.
Kanon-kun will definitely be able to see it.
After all-
Without love, it cannot be seen.
Master?
Who's there?
It's me, Kanon.
The weather is heavy. Will it get worse?
Yes, the forecast says so. Should I bring an umbrella?
This is unnecessary. You should leave me alone for a while.
I am busy on a journey through my own thoughts.
...Certainly. Then, if you would excuse me.
Ooohhh, Beatrice.
...Why, why does my hand not reach Beatrice's smile?!
What do you do to be resurrected? What do you do to be smiling at me again?
What can I do to see your face again?
You... stay away from the Master!
You fool, Kinzo... Can't you see me, even though I am here?
What do I have to do to get my hands on your smile?
Is it the age of the moon? The cycle of the comet? Is it the arrangement of the planets? What is lacking?
What is, what is?!
It's useless, Kinzo. ...Without love, it cannot be seen.
...Would I be able see something I couldn't have seen before?
Beatrice!
Without love, it cannot be seen.
Even so, we are also furniture that could not become human.
K-Kanon-kun... actually, I'd like to ask you a favor.
Good morning Jessie!
Jessieee! Is your boyfriend here?
AH!
Ah, it seems he's not here yet.
Maybe he's busy with work?
What kind of person is Jessie's boyfriend?
At least give us a hint.
Awesome, he's a working man, right?
Suits? Glasses?
So how about finding someone to pretend to be Milady's boyfriend and take him with you?
F- fake? Wh-who...?! I can't think of, anyone...!
For example, what about Kanon-kun?
Kanon-kun?! No way, no way!
Isn't it nice? This is an opportunity to hangout with Kanon!
Ehhh?
But... but, but, but, BUT...
AaaahhHHH!
Jessie, we have a visitor.
Eh? Could it be!?
Kanon-kun!
I didn't know where the stairs were. I apologize for being late.
R- right, umm... that outfit suits you, doesn't it?
Shouta boyfriend is heeere!
...What should I do, Milady?
Don't call me Milady!!
He calls himself "boku" and she makes him call her Milady, like a butler!
Kanon-kun, could you close your eyes for just three seconds?
Sorry, nothing happened!
Anyway, let's go to the stage! I have to get ready...
...School?
What a noisy place.
I think it's important to always stay composed and dignified.
But, seeing Milady just now... I can understand Natsuhi's headache a little.
Speaking of which, Madame Natsuhi, as PTA president, should have attended the ceremony in the gymnasium.
Is she going to see Milady's performance?
Excuse me! Are you by yourself?
Would you like to join us?
If a girl starts talking to you, all you have to say are these magic words!
I'm sorry. I'm with someone.
Gaaaaaah!
God, this might be my type!
My masochistic blood is boiling!
You lied to me!
That's what the book said!
Found you! Come on!
I'm never coming here again...
Thank you for coming!
I... hate fantasies.
Honestly, I really want to get out of here.
But, the truth is...
I can't look away.
Thank you everyone, enjoy the rest of the show!
The young lady on stage is not at all like what the young lady of Ushiromiya should be.
But watching Milady have so much fun, I thought,
Is this the true form of Ushiromiya Jessica?
I worked close to Milady, saw her in all seasons, and I thought I knew everything about her.
But that was only limited to one side of her, Milady of Rokkenjima.
We are furniture. We serve on Rokkenjima, and live out our lives on Rokkenjima.
But today, I feel like I can see something that 'cannot be seen' on Rokkenjima.
Without love, it cannot be seen.
I still can't think of the ocean as blue.
Mom, look, it's cute, isn't it?
Jessica, you once again bought something with no taste.
Mom, today Mira and I...
I've always told you to choose your friends, right?
Hey, Mom!
Get dressed. The piano teacher is coming.
Your awareness as a member of the Ushiromiya family is far from enough.
I hate studying and thick books that took away all my fun.
But the thing I hated the most was myself that giving up every day like that.
Oh, Jessica - wasn't the cultural festival today?
Yeah, I guess.
I was watching. You did a good job.
Really?
You appeared with both composure and dignity. Fitting behavior for the students' representative.
...Ah.
The experience of standing above people and bearing responsibility will definitely be useful in the future.
Krauss-sama, the guests are already waiting in the living room.
Ah. I'll be there right away.
Anyway, even if she came, she would definitely say something like "it wasn't appropriate for the successor to the Ushiromiya family".
Milady.
Wah! Kanon-kun.
Thank you so much for coming to cheer me on today!
Your singing... it was good.
Eh?
Ahahaha, really? I'm embarrassed.
I can't sing, because I'm furniture.
Kanon-kun, enough with that phrase "because I am furniture".
You're a human just like me.
I...
Kanon-kun, when you saw me singing... what did you think?
It looked like you were having a lot of fun.
That's... not completely true.
Eh?
You were jealous, weren't you?
That isn't...
I know I'm the successor to the Ushiromiya family or something... I'm sure there'll be a lot of annoying stuff to do in the future.
I've just gotta resign myself to it.
Yes, that may be true.
But there's one place where you and I are completely different.
Different?
I can't accept this kind of fate, so I do the best I can.
I've created another self that can do everything I like.
People are always making another part of themselves inside themselves that they can really like.
Inside themselves...?
Kanon is the name given to you in the Gospel House. It's not your real name, right?
Yes.
Then, it should be alright to have times when you're Kanon-kun, and times when you aren't.
I think you can live much, much more freely!
A time when, I am not Kanon.
So if you don't mind, tell me.
What's your real name?
I forgot.
Eh?
Even if I did have a name,
The only truth now is that here, I am Kanon.
I told you to stop that! You're human.
I am not human!
Kanon-kun!
Milady, you are human!
But it's cruel to ask furniture to talk about dreams like this.
Why? Why are you saying that?
Shannon told me. Something about Milady taking a liking to me.
Eh? Ah, that.
But, I can't pretend to be a human.
I cannot delude myself like Shannon.
How can you say that?
People cannot love furniture.
Even if Milady can love furniture, I cannot love Milady.
That's all what I wanted to say.
If your feelings for me are due to my conceit, then please forgive me.
And thank you so much for treating me as human.
No, that's enough.
Umm... sorry.
No, I am also...
If I don't go back to my room, mom will get mad at me again.
I wish you a good night, Milady.
Yeah... good night.
Nice going, making a woman cry like that.
Had you answered normally, another pair of lovers would have been born with my magic.
Just now, I figured it out.
You are just a demon who enjoys showing love to those who can never be joined, and deceiving them.
Furniture is a thoroughly pitiful existence.
Shannon and George will also eventually reach a stalemate with their love, an ending that suits the tastes of me.
You!
You didn't think I would lend them that power without any compensation?
I'll lend a hand in love.
My compensation shall be one ticket to watch the cruel fate that the two of them will eventually meet.
Even after one thousand years, no better show exists!
Just look at Kinzo!
You really are a witch! Disappear and get out of my sight, you demon!
I shall disappear without being asked. My power still hasn't returned.
Just like a low tide without the moon, my magical power will surely rise,
and I will surely have my return, at a time that is appropriate for me,
and rule as the true master of the island.
At that time, the door to the Golden Land will be opened again.
The covetous and greedy shall call me forth without fail!
Beatrice...
Why do you leave me alone in this sea of suffering?
I yearn after you this much!
Master, drinking any more will be damaging to your health.
Be silent, Genji. You do not understand, you do not understand my grief and sadness!
What? Furniture, Furniture? How ridiculous!
Why did you leave me alone, Beatrice?
Tonight, two seeds of love have been sown.
Including the one already sown, that makes three.
I look forward to seeing how they ripen!
What do you mean by that?
I mean what I said. I still haven't built up my castle. Once I think of myself as an adult for the first time...
I want to marry you.
So I want to give you an engagement ring.
Engagement...
I will probably bring a ring to the family conference coming up soon.
Please, I want you to let me hear your answer.
If you accept, I will proclaim our marriage to all of the relatives, including Grandfather.
But...
No matter what anyone says, I will make you happy.
I promise.
Let's go, Maria. Hurry.
Uu-uu! I want Halloween.
I want to dress up like a witch!
The family conference isn't for playing. We're going to meet Grandfather, so you have to wear western clothes.
Halloween! Halloween!
Trick or treat! Trick or treat! Uu-uu-uu-!
I told you to stop saying "Uu-uu"!
For the lovely Witch.
Uu-!
Got a sweet, got a sweet! Look, look, Mama, Mama! Happy Hallowee~n!
Hey Maria, you can't just accept sweets from strangers, right? Return it.
It's alright, ho ho ho. She's a lovely young lady. How old is she?
Maria, give the candy back.
Uu-! Uu-!! Maria got that!!
Let go of it!
Thank you for your kindness.
Sorry.
Uu-uu-!! No, Maria's candy!!
Maria's candy!!
Don't I always tell you not to say uu-uu-!!
I told you to be quiet!
Uu-uu, Mama, it hurts! Uu-uu!!
That's why I'm telling you to shut up!!
That's the reason you can't make friends in class, right?!
Why are you still crying? Why? Why?!
Mama, it hurts...! Mama, save me...! Uu-uu-uu-uu-!!
It's because you're like this that Papa's business trip doesn't end!!
It's because you...
I've... done it again...
Mama! Mama, come back...!
-uu-uu-uu-!!
Maria, I'm sorry... I'm sorry!
Mama... welcome back...
Forgive your bad Mama... I'm really sorry! Please, don't hate your Mama...
Mama was only being possessed by an evil witch again... But, Mama came back, so it's fine.
...Do you want to celebrate Halloween, Maria?
Yeah. I wanted to show the pumpkin marshmallow to George onii-chan and Jessica onee-chan...
Okay. Then Maria,
I don't know if they sell it in this town or not, but let's get off and try searching for it, okay?
Uu, ...yeah! Love you so much Mama, love you!
I love you too, Maria. Maybe we won't find a marshmallow exactly like that one, but it's alright if there's a similar sweet, right?
Yeah! If it's a sweet I bought together with Mama, anything is fine!
Dear, what are you doing in a place like this?
Oh, it's you. It's nothing.
I'm finishing all of today's preparations. For now, shall we relax and wait while drinking tea?
Sorry. I'm always pushing all my problems on you.
Please, can't you rely on me more?
I am your wife.
Naturally, I'm grateful for you always coming to my aid.
That's why we have to get through today.
The topic of Father's inheritance, right?
Is everything okay with Father?
No problem. Genji and Doctor Nanjo are on our side.
I'll never allow those greedy siblings to meet Father.
Then, the kitchen is all yours.
Of course, thank you.
Please leave everything to me, Gohda.
All the relatives will come visit today.
See that you do not make any blunders.
Yes, I will keep in mind.
Moreover...
Today, we welcome an important guest in the truest sense.
Make sure you're prepared,
Kanon.
Yes.
The lawyer said that the situation is pretty rough.
If I knew this would happen, I wouldn't have started this many projects in the company...
President!
Aah, calm down, you bastards.
If we gather the money, we'll be able to settle everything.
I'll figure it out. If it goes well, I'll treat you all to a champagne tower.
So just shut up and follow me, alright?
Yes president!
Honey, are you okay?
Ah, well... has Rosa not arrived yet?
Not yet. She is pretty late.
Fortunately, because of the typhoon, the flight was delayed, but she's still too slow.
As a brother, you still treat your sister as a child no matter how old you are.
Hah! Dad's always a kid, no matter how old he gets.
What are you talking about? If I was a kid, you'd be a baby.
Stop that! Are you seriously a kid?
Six years later, you're still my kid.
What you did to mom six years ago, I haven't forgotten.
Battler-kun, let's not talk about this.
Sorry we're late!
You're so slow, Rosa!
Hoh, Maria-chan! Long time no see!
Hello everyone, it's been so long!
Oh, is that Battler-kun? He's really grown up!
Everyone I've met today had to say that once! How embarassing...
Uu —? Who is it?
Last time I saw you, you were three years old. You don't remember me, do you?
Maria, this is Battler onii-chan.
Uncle Rudolf's son. Understand?
Get away from me!
Oh, that must be for Halloween?
Uu-uu! Halloween, Halloween! Battler knows about that, too?
Hey, you have to call him Battler onii-chan, right?
I don't mind that.
Come on, let's go!
Battler-kun!
That guy is really...
Speaking of Halloween, what about costumes? What does Maria want to dress up as?
Uu —! The witch, Beatrice!
Huh? Bea? What did you say?
Let's go. It's almost time.
If you don't hurry up, we're going to leave you guys behind.
Oh, oh, okay, Maria, let's hurry. Woosh!
Woooooosh!
Oh, Milady, what are you doing here?
Kumasawa-san. When the day of the family conference comes, for some reason, I feel curious about this witch.
Why is that?
The family conference is the day when everyone related to Grandfather gathers.
Isn't it true that Battler is also coming today after six years?
So I was wondering if there might be relatives who have not appeared in decades showing up.
If there is such a thing, this year's family conference will become like a typhoon, right?
Kumasawa-san, you know more about Beatrice, don't you?
The only thing I can say is that Beatrice-sama is the Witch of Gold.
She is the other master who controls the night of this island.
Isn't that just second hand talk from Grandfather?
But, I can at least say this much.
What?
In ancient times, Rokkenjima was feared, and called Azukijima (Evil Appetite Island).
The story told among the fishermen is that "Azuki" was a mispronunciation of "Akujiki."
I've also heard that. The fishermen were afraid because of the sunken rocks and shipwrecks, right?
And then, a traveling mountaineering ascetic or someone built that shrine, reposed the souls and settled them there.
That shrine for the repose of souls was destroyed by an eerie violet thunderbolt this summer, which tore up the darkness of the night.
The evil spirits of Akujikishima woke up from their sleep, and summoned Beatrice-sama.
Eh? What are you talking about?
If Beatrice-sama happened to come for the family conference...
If she happened to come...?
Could it be that you don't plan on appearing at the family conference this year either?
I don't want to join in on the argument of those vultures.
Today, I will... hold a certain ceremony.
A ceremony?
It would be more accurate to call it a gamble... Because miracles do not dwell in magic that doesn't bear risks.
So as your friend, I can only pray from the bottom of my heart that you will win this ceremony.
Speaking of that, Kinzo-san. Did you hear that a longed-for guest will be at the family meeting this year?
What?
Right, Battler-kun from Rudolf-san's family. I hear he will be coming after six years.
Oh, Battler? I wouldn't call him 'longed for', a guest who doesn't show up for six years.
Possibly, a truly longed-for guest... will pay us a visit.
Everything depends on the results of the roulette.
What is it? I'm busy.
Genji speaking. Everyone has arrived.
In total, 18 people.
Now then, all the pieces are lined up.
Do you have a problem?
Nope.
Don't you tell me you don't have a plan...?
How do you know what you're going to do before you know what you're going to do?
Since I don't know your moves, I don't have any plan. Feel free to take the initiative.
Now... in what way shall I destroy your defense? With how many moves will I checkmate you? It's an opportunity to display my skills.
Whatever moves you come at me with, I won't believe you!
As long as I stand my ground on that point, I won't lose. The way this game is made, you cannot win!
Maybe you're right. However, you know what? I'll decide how many times we'll repeat this game.
It will be repeated over and over again, until I win and you recognize your defeat, okay...?
In other words, this is torture.
Then, Beatrice... I have only one thing to tell you before we start.
You're free to say anything.
However, whether I'll believe you or not, is something I'll decide for myself!
You think this is torture for me?
You're wrong!
Then, what are you talking about...!
Someday, you will yield to me and give up.
Until then, this is torture for you!
How amusing, a fine metaphor!
Come then.
We shall begin that torture,
Urshiromiya Battleeeeeer!
Ah, not much is different this year.
Uu —! This is from Maria!
Oh, thank you.
Hey, Aniki, why do you think Maria likes Halloween so much?
Hmm, well, she is the 'witch' Maria-chan.
A witch?
Maria, is there some relation between witches and Halloween?
Ah, Battler...
Uu —! The ancient Celts thought the sun would die at the end of October.
Then, after resting its body in the land of the dead, it would resurrect again on the winter solstice day.
They called the day that the sun ended its one year lifespan and died New Year's Eve, or Samhain.
Hoh! Even I never knew Halloween had such a history.
Uu —! So Halloween is the time when the power of witches and demons is at its most vigorous and prosperous!
I'm sure Beatrice will come!
And then, we'll eat marshmallow candies together, and she'll bring Maria to the Golden Land with her!
...Uu!
My, my, isn't that wonderful.
By the way, Rosa, how old is Maria this year?
Maria, stop talking about that.
Gohda-san, can you take everyone to the guest house?
Certainly. Well then, everyone, I will guide you to the guesthouse.
Mama?
Don't you have work to do?
Even though I'm always telling you not to talk about witches... Haven't I always said that was our promise together...?
Mama, it hurts, Mama, it hurts!
You're so noisy with that 'Halloween, Halloween'... ridiculous, isn't it? You're nine years old!
We were even late because I bought that disgusting monster marshmallow.
How much more will you have to embarrass me before you're satisfied?
Disgusting, disgusting! That's what you are, that's what you are!
Come back, Mama... Save me, Mama... Beat the bad witch...
I told you to stop saying witch!
Mama, Mama...!
Why don't you just stay there doing that forever!
Maria-sama, are you all right?
Uu...
She's a horrible person. I can't believe that was a mother...
It can't be helped. Maria can handle that much. Maria is just fine...!
I'll exchange it for something I received earlier.
Oh, this was from Rosa-sama.
You know, it would be easy for Beatrice to repair it!
Maria-sama... you know about Beatrice?
You know, Maria is friends with Beatrice. Why don't we meet her today and play?
Father said that he was very busy with his research. He said that, unfortunately, he will be unable to make an appearance.
Good grief. He's really not attending this year?
Doctor Nanjo. Is it really a problem with his research and his mood?
He isn't already bedridden, and unable to get up, right?
Well... I wonder. There is not much I can say...
Father is steadily regaining his health.
Although if he's that energetic, I wish he'd at least come to greet us.
Don't say that.
If he were here, you would complain the whole time about how you couldn't relax.
Haven't you two quickly become respectful of Father now that his remaining life has been announced?
What are you trying to say?
Quit it, Aneki.
There should be a few things that the siblings couldn't talk to him about before forming a unified opinion, right?
Yep! We must take this precious time seriously and talk together modestly.
Okay, then let's hear it.
Your precious, important talk.
Maria-chan really has grown a lot this past year.
Does it look that way?
Of course.
It's because she has such an affectionate mother with her.
I...am not qualified to be a mother.
Children can't choose their parents. That poor girl...
Doesn't that go both ways?
A parent can't choose what kind of child is born, too.
It isn't a matter of who is at fault.
Isn't everything alright as long as you slowly watch over her as she grows up, with living together on your mind?
Maria-chan has grown up a lot.
Thank you very much.
Is it raining?
That's right... I told her,
"Just stay there doing that forever."
Huh? But she must have already...
Maria is that kind of child!
What, what happened?
I'm sorry!
What is it?
Just let her be. More importantly, should we continue?
Hmm.
Maria! Are you here? If you're here, answer me!
Maria!
Uu —?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Mama isn't bad... She was just possessed by a bad witch again.
I'm sorry... Mama lost to the bad witch, forgive me...
I really like Mama. I love you!
So, Maria. Why don't you come back to the mansion with Mama?
Uu — I'm not coming.
Why?
It's Beatrice. She'll come really soon. So I'm waiting.
Really... Then instead of waiting here, why don't we wait in the mansion?
Come! Beatrice will co-me!
And when she does, I'll give a candy to Beatrice. I'll do trick-or-treat!
I'll give her a jack-o-lantern marshmallow candy and say Happy Halloween!
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuu—!!
Beatrice!
It's been a while. Have you been healthy?
Uu—! Maria is well! Beatrice, Happy Halloween!
Mmm. Happy Halloween.
The candy has become like this.
Uu —, stepped on and smashed.
Can Beato return it to normal?
It will be easy.
Come, Maria. Close your eyes and try to remember.
What kind of candy was it really?
It can't be...
You may now open your eyes.
Beatrice is always awesome, awesome!
Does my face look familiar? If you stare so fixedly, you might burn a hole through it.
I'm sorry.
Maria. I will give this to you in exchange for that sweet.
Uu —, letter?
The time will soon come that you may open it, but until then, you definitely must not.
It will become an invitation calling you to the Golden Land.
Golden Land! Finally take Maria there! Uu —!
And this, is for you.
This is... dad's special envelope!
The fact that I have met you here probably means that you were chosen by Kinzo's roulette.
Take it, then read its contents aloud while seated at the dinner table, when all of the siblings are gathered.
Eh?
Let us meet later.
Allow me to name myself in that place.
We have been awaiting you... Beatrice-sama.
It's been a while, Genji. Is Kinzo well?
He is very well.
Then let us greet him. It will be good to hurl curses at each other after thirty years.
Pleased to meet you.
Rudolf's second wife?
That is correct.
My name is Kyrie.
I wonder if this is our first meeting.
Even though you have a vague idea, you dare to ask my name?
How long has it been since he left this place?
I believe it has already been several years.
Did he want to make me a bird in a cage that much? How pitiful.
Beatrice-sama...
What is this? A magic ward! Is that person unable to get by without relying on something like this?
Shall I open it?
No... it is fine.
Allow me to enjoy the final gamble and fall of an aged mage, who fell in love with me and threw away all his life!
Allow me to enjoy my game with you.
Excuse me... I have brought lunch, Beatrice-sama.
It has been a long time... Furniture called Kanon.
It has... been a long time...
I came to resolve my final promise with Kinzo.
Your final promise with... Master?
I lent Kinzo a mountain of gold.
When Kinzo gives that up, it will be returned to me with interest.
I came here tonight to receive that.
Could it be... You...
Behold the sweetfish river running through my beloved hometown...
That's the witch's epitaph!
The day when everything will be returned to the Golden Land has come.
Rejoice.
The day when the shame of your time as furniture will end has finally come.
That is fine with me.
But, Shannon will now have emotions that she must not know,
and will probably have a very hard time forced upon her.
That kind of attachment is the greatest joy for a witch!
I thank you for gifting us furniture the day of our release.
And, I hate you for making this day difficult for Shannon to accept!
If you want to kill me, try to do it.
However, if you kill me, the day of rest for the furniture will not come for all eternity.
If you want that,
Kneel.
Kneel and kiss my shoes.
Otherwise, I'll leave this place and never show myself again for all eternity.
What!
If the door to the Golden Land is opened, your life as furniture will end.
If you desire, I will even give you life as a human.
I know it, you grew jealous seeing Shannon wallow in the swamp of sweet love.
You are sorely tempted to know the taste of love.
Stop it, stop it! I won't be reduced to a toy to please you!
Hoh. Then I will be satisfied with Shannon.
At the second twilight, those who remain shall tear apart the two who are close.
Don't you think that there is no one more fitting to be a sacrifice for the second twilight than Shannon as she is now?
What a dirty...
What will you do, Kanon?
If you kneel, I'll surely hold back from choosing Shannon as a sacrifice, okay?
What the shit is this? This is just demented!
It's because your argument regarding 18 or 19 people, which you are using as a basis to deny me, is truly humorous.
So much so that I tried changing my move.
There's no way I can accept something like this, right?!
A witch came in, walking right through the entrance hall, you say?!
Don't mess with me!
What's this? In the last game, I let you make your moves terribly freely, right?
Will you give in already after the first move?
This much isn't even close to enough to make me accept something like a witch.
Just now you only made it look like you had fixed Maria's candy with magic. It's not magic!
I see. Is that your move in response to mine?
Ah?
You've dug your own grave, Ushiromiya Battler.
Allow me to continue my move. It has barely begun, the Turn of the Witch!
That is a big yawn, Battler-kun.
With all the tension resolved, I started to get sleepy, listening to the sound of the rain.
Uu —? Battler's asleep? A nap?
Even though we've finally gathered all the cousins together after six years.
This guy doesn't have a clue that he's the main guest of this family conference, does he?
I've casually eaten lunch, and there's even a typhoon and rain.
Since we aren't doing anything, that means it isn't my turn yet.
You're always the main character of your own life, right? Why are you acting like a supporting actor?
It seems like he's already backstage.
I can't pretend not to hear that!
I think he's got that kind of personality where he doesn't want to get up on the stage because he can't be the main character.
Jessica-chan.
When are you going to get up on the stage?
Seems like around 20 years old.
I told her my name, but she didn't tell me hers.
Was this person trying to say that she was... the witch of the portrait?
I have never seen a blonde woman like that.
Me neither.
If this woman claims to be Beatrice, what is her purpose?
It's obvious! She'll insist she's a legitimate successor of the inheritance.
Father is still a slave to Beatrice.
If they had that daughter, he'd hand over the whole fortune to her.
Or, maybe she plans to call herself his mistress's daughter, and demand that the inheritance be distributed to her.
We desperately need a large amount of money urgently because of our circumstances.
Kyrie, could you use the chessboard thinking to reason out her goal?
It's the first I've heard of it, but one of the premises here is that we have an urgent need to collect money, right?
What's this?
That's right.
Her unexpected visit was kept hidden from us.
I don't know what her surprise is, but she's been hiding it until today.
Which means that, it seems her goal is one that would be disadvantageous to her if we did interact.
I get it. If she had a will or something that could prove that she was acknowledged as a blood relative...
If she thought it was rock-solid proof, then you'd think she'd actually have announced it beforehand.
So, that would mean that, from the time she first aimed for a surprise attack, we know the enemy couldn't win in a frontal attack.
To skip to the conclusion, it will probably be something related either directly or indirectly to the inheritance problem.
Even if this carries with it a significant impact, it is not absolute.
In other words, no matter what our opponent brings up, we interact calmly, without rushing things.
What I don't know about is the connection between her and Krauss nii-san.
If Krauss nii-san called her here, it might make things troublesome.
Let's handle it like this. As long as she can't clearly prove her identity, we won't accept her position.
No matter who she is, we won't admit it.
Right. In other words, whatever is shown to us now on Rokkenjima cannot be accepted as true.
She will have to wait until the typhoon goes away and prove it to us at the proper place.
Recklessly finding fault in that kind of thing is Aneki's specialty.
We all need money urgently!
How can we let our hopes to get the inheritance be crushed by a mysterious woman like this?!
Maria. Today at noon, who was that woman we met outside?
Uu —... I've said it many times, she's Beatrice.
Maria, have you ever met Beatrice before, at this mansion?
Uu —! We meet every year.
Every year?
Does she live here?
Uu —! Beatrice lives on this island because she is the witch of Rokkenjima.
Then, even when there is no family meeting she's on this island, right?
Uu — ... Mhm!
How could this be, it's unbelievable. When?...
I lived on this island. I spent my time in this mansion.
However, I have never met a witch like that...
What's wrong, Mama?
What's wrong with my head?
Mama, are you okay? Mama?!
Kanon-kun!
You're going to the VIP room, right?
Mm. I heard that the visitor is Beatrice-sama, is that true?
She came to open the doors to the Golden Land and return everything back there!
It can't be, why now of all times?
Didn't I tell you? We are furniture!
Because we acted like humans, because of love... we can't obediently accept the day when our service is over!
It's my fault.
She joined you together, planning to use you and George-sama as the sacrifices of the second twilight.
Do you understand? By tempting you, Nee-san, she took advantage of you!
That's right.
But she told me,
she promised that if you don't accept the engagement ring tonight, she won't choose you as a sacrifice.
Our salvation is in the Golden Land!
If we can make it that far, we can become human!
Kanon-kun.
Together. Let's go.
To start a real life.
If we do that, I wonder if I will be able to know love as well.
I wonder if I'll stop making people cry.
I... don't want to be furniture anymore!
I won't apologize. I'm a witch, after all.
For what?
You heard it, right? What saved your romance was my doing.
My sheer mischievious heart.
It was nothing more than a seed I sowed to see how it would twist and fall apart.
No matter your ulterior motive, you gave me the magic of love.
Nothing will change this fact.
So, I won't hold a grudge against you.
Thank you for teaching me to be human.
I am no longer furniture.
Truly frustrating, furniture.
I am not furniture.
Be silent.
I won't be silent.
I finally came to understand people like you.
So, I'm now sure that this is the way to resist you.
What is it?
I will have nothing to do with you.
I will carry out the fate that has been given to me. So, I won't entertain you.
Nothing to do with you...?
So, there's such a way to resist? I like it!
I'll kill you, together with your beloved one!
If that is the fate that you have decided, that is up to you.
If you think that will bore me, that's a huge misunderstanding.
That just made my interest in your final moments grow hotter and hotter!
Okay. Now if you'll excuse me...
Oh?
This is getting interesting after all!
I suppose I'm not so old yet.
This is why I am still not tired of living after one thousand years!
Today's main course is calf steak.
To accompany, I have a Bordelaise sauce.
Of course, the red wine base I used was excellent even among those made in Bordeaux.
In addition, I prepared an original blend of this house.
It is a blend of choice alcohol from around the world to further deepen the taste.
This sauce is limited to this year.
It would greatly please me if you were to enjoy yourselves.
So...
Yes, Kyrie-sama!
There are 18 relatives and servants on this island...
but, I believe I heard a guest was coming today?
Yes, she wished to have her meal alone in the VIP room.
VIP Room?
Who are you talking about?
It's... Beatrice-sama.
Beatrice? Is this that Beatrice?
Uu —!
Gohda, is that also some side show for the dinner?
Let's stop with this cheap play. Aniki, you've called her.
Nii-san, let's be honest. Who is she?
Don't you tell me that she is really the Beatrice of the portrait?
Wait, I have no idea what you're talking about.
Gohda, call for Genji right now!
So, Aniki, you don't know either?
In other words, did Father call her here?
That's right. Could she be Father's mistress or something like that?
The head wouldn't have something as filthy as a mistress!
In the first place, where did that woman come from?
The only boat trip today was the one which brought you all.
Oh my, how could you prove that there were no other boats besides the one we were on?
You can't prove "she didn't come"!
We just need someone to say they saw her to prove the opposite.
In fact, Kyrie met that woman.
What did you say?
It's not possible to prove "she didn't come".
Even if everyone says they haven't seen her,
It is also impossible to deny the possibility that "she came secretly."
I see. So, that's the "Devil's proof", right?
What we can be sure of is that she came to this manson with some kind of goal.
Isn't it obvious? She probably intends to claim right over Father's inheritance!
Everyone, wait a minute! Genji-san will be coming soon. He will definitely answer our questions.
Let's put that aside until then.
Feels like it's getting interesting.
Ohh!
Wait. Kids, return to the guesthouse.
Eeeeeh?!
It's easy to prove a devil, as long as you meet one.
But... it's impossible to prove that one "doesn't exist".
Even if no one's ever seen one, it's not evidence of "not existing."
Then, what I saw was...
I'm very sorry I'm late! I already called Genji here.
Excuse me. Is there anything I can help you with?
Yes, you can. Plenty.
Genji-san, please answer honestly.
Who is that Beatrice in the VIP room now?
But I didn't expect that the witch Beatrice-sama would actually show up.
Doctor Nanjo and Grandfather have been friends for a long time, right?
Is there such a person for Grandfather?
Oh, a mistress?
You idiot...!
Eh?
Yes, but I've never met her.
I have heard that she passed away a long time ago.
Did they have kids?
I don't know.
It's just, Kinzo-san was always doing research to ressurrect Beatrice.
If he had a child with his late mistress, he would probably shed all his love onto them.
So, those two probably didn't have a child.
That's also a "Devil's proof".
There is no way to prove it doesn't exist.
Could it really be that the illegitimate child returned to the island to take revenge on Grandfather?
Revenge? You've watched too many strange TV shows.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, but there are 18 people on this island.
Yeah, there is no way to do anything suspicious.
Besides, even if you use the name of the witch,
What can one human woman who can't use magic even do?
That's Battler's understanding of things.
What?
Battler doesn't believe the 19th guest, Beatrice, is a witch, right?
Of course not.
There is no way witches exist.
What? That's a "Devil's proof"! There is no way witches do exist?
You can only ask the Witch's side to make a rebuttal. This is also a Devils's proof.
If she shows herself, this will be all over.
Show us something that is impossible for a human.
Both of you, stop it!
If that's what you want, then Beatrice will surely show you.
Then Battler will believe in her as well right? In Beatrice.
Yeah, then I'll believe it. I guess.
Speaking of, where is George-aniki?
Don't do that. Why are you also laughing?
What's going on?
Eh? Wait, Aniki, where did you go?
Sayo,
I'll make you my wife.
That's what this ring is for.
Thank you, George.
I'm not just looking at how you are now.
I'm gazing at you as you will be in the future too.
You always tell me that, how you want to slowly grow old surrounded by healthy children and grandchildren.
Slowly spending the time while getting old.
And when we're old, you will be by my side.
I predicted this day would come
Please show me that future.
I promise that even if we become souls, we will always be together.
Yes.
I... I want you to put that ring on, whatever finger you like, and have that be your answer.
Umm, so, by tomorrow morning...
This is my answer, George-san.
Sayo!
There was no blessing from God, no pastor to witness, nothing.
But, two souls were joined here today...
Nee-san, are you an idiot?
Why did you wear the ring even though you knew it would go unfulfilled?
Because, we agreed to be together forever.
In that instant, our eternity was complete.
So, it's alright.
You're lying...
Kanon-kun, why do you want to be human?
Because, I liked Milady!
And after seeing Milady that day,
I liked her even more!
I was just afraid...
I thought that if love could not be eternal, I was better off without it!
Beatrice-sama is detestable.
But, the witch's expectations are probably off.
After all...
Knowing love isn't a regret that ties you to life.
It is the place we should reach on our journey through life...
I have no objections. Natsuhi and I accept it.
Us too.
I also accept it. No doubt.
I also accept. This is your victory.
You've proven the devil.
Kyrie, do you still have any objections?
I don't like it unless everyone's together.
I'm sorry, I surrender.
I have to accept you are the consultant alchemist of the Ushiromiya family, and a witch.
It begins.
It's morning...
In any event, it seems that I've escaped being one of the first sacrifices.
Well then Beatrice, which six pieces did you take?
My defense is perfect, I will not shame myself like last time!
Genji-san?
Did something happen?
I apologize for waking you this early.
Yes... actually, at the chapel...
What is this?
When I went to the dining hall to clean up the tea set, there was a memo with 'chapel' written on it...
Rosa-sama... look at this.
Happy HALLOWEEN for MARIA
I'll go check on Maria and come back. Go tell Krauss nii-san and the rest!
We tried to contact Krauss-sama, but could not find him...
Have you checked inside the chapel?
No, not yet.
The chapel lock is special, so the master key does not work. Only a single key can open it.
But, that key is missing from the key box.
Rosa-sama!
The time to open that will come soon.
I knew it...
Aunt Rosa?
What's wrong? Are you awake, Battler?
Yeah, I felt like I saw something...
Behold the sweetfish river running through my beloved hometown.
You who seek the Golden Land, follow its path downstream in search of the key.
I don't know why I feel so uneasy.
Why is the Witch's epitaph circling my mind?
The one who obtains the key must then travel to the Golden Land in accordance with these rules.
What happens... when you get there?
Speaking of which, why do I care about this kind of thing?
The game between us and the witch is about to begin.
Why?
On the first twilight, offer the six chosen by the key as sacrifices.
Offer up the sacrifice.
My heart hurts...
I don't want to live anymore.
But...
That's for the chapel... Where did you find it?
I'm going to open it.
Everyone?
Are you sleeping?
Rosa-sama...
Ambulance! Police!
Dad!!
DON'T LOOK!!
Father!! Mother!!
Do you know why? When you denied my existence in the last game, you thought in a certain way.
Their faces are crushed, so the identities of the corpses cannot be confirmed.
Therefore, the possibility that fake corpses had been prepared to create an alibi cannot be eliminated. Because of that, the human culprit theory can be maintained!
So this time I left the bodies intact. Oh, this makes it easy to narrow down the suspect.
I'll drag out your guts!!
Come on, Battler, try to deny the corpses in front of you.
The culprit could be human, right?
Doubt your loved ones, deny the witch dancing in madness on the stage of blood!
I'm not crying... Damn it, damn it, I won't cry!
Even if we cry, the reality of what has happened here won't change.
Madam, something's wrong within the mansion. The phone seems to be out of order. The emergency radio is not working either.
What are you saying? Does that mean we can't contact the police?
It's that person! They did something to the phone line, and killed Dad and Mom!
Milady!
Unforgivable! Damn it, damn it, DAMN IT!
Please wait.
So, it has begun, Beatrice.
It's not like anyone can solve this riddle anyway. So Beato will definitely win.
Hurry up and open the door to the Golden Land and take me away!
Gohda-san, leave it to me.
Understood.
I'll double-check the VIP room and go back to the chapel.
Gohda-san. If you find her... tell me right away.
Of course.
Milady... I'm afraid Beatrice has already-
I know! I read the message in the VIP room.
Did you think I'd be that senile, to just sit around here waiting for you to come barging in to kill me?
These stupid parents have now filled their bellies in the land of sweets!
Milady! Are you okay?
I'm fine... I'm fine.
Mom and Dad are gone...
I'll be in the corridor. If you need something, please call me immediately.
Ah— ...
Do you need something?
Sorry, it's nothing...
I don't even know what to do...
That is why I am...
That's why you're furniture.
Beatrice!
For the second twilight sacrifice, I will pick the two of you.
W- wait! That's not the kind of relationship we have!
Fine, then I will only kill Jessica.
Why would you do that?!
Milady!
Why? To see the pained look on your face. Why else?
Kanon-kun!
Make me laugh as hard as I can, furniture of Kinzo!
Milady, I'm here to protect you!
I'll beat you down to the hell you came from!
Kanon-kun, what's that?
I didn't want to show you.
Go ahead!
Am I dreaming?
Oh? It seems that you're not all useless.
It's your turn, Beatrice!
It was quite an interesting show. I was going to let you get away. But now, your rudeness has caused me to change my mind...
I won't let you kill Milady!
Don't talk, furniture.
Be quiet, furniture.
Know your place, furniture!
Kanon-kun isn't furniture, he is a human!
Why can you say that?
Kanon-kun... he rushed in to save me of his own will,
and he stood in the path of a fearsome witch, you!
Milady...
Self-sacrifice is part the noble spirit that only humans have.
Kanon-kun is a human!!
Don't speak, little girl.
Come, arise, forgive the sin, one of the seven stakes of Purgatory,
Lust!
Asmodeus of Lust, right here.
I've had enough of this farce. Quickly, execute the second twilight. Don't keep me waiting, alright?
As you command.
Kanon-kun!
Oh? Are you scared? How cute.
Hey hey, where do you want it? Where do you want me to pierce you? Answer me, cutie boy. Wherever you want it, I'll run you through hard!
Shut up!
Come on, try to chase me, you blind idiot!
This is...
Milady!
My guess was... spot on...
Serves you... right...
What's wrong, Kanon?
I thought Milady Jessica wasn't going to be killed before you?
Yes, yes, that's it, that's it! That face, that look on your face is what I wanted to see!
How truly enjoyable!
Come, arise, forgive the sin, one of the seven stakes of Purgatory,
Wrath!
Satan of Wrath, right here.
That furniture, close the curtain on his stage.
I'm not furniture anymore...
And now, I won't doubt that again!
Your chest... It's so warm, and it feels so good to pierce it, okay...? Come on, let me have another taste, alright...?
Won't you make me feel good?
Sorry... I couldn't... protect you.
You don't need to worry... Kanon-kun... You aren't furniture anymore...
Ah...
I wanted to ask you... what your real name was...
My... real name is...
I... became... human...
Even after a hundred years, furniture is furniture, fool! I'll tell you what it really means to disgrace the dead.
I see, so it has begun?
Yes.
Shannon. I shall be writing a will. Please copy what I say.
Well then. If I am to speak of my life, I must begin writing from when I met that witch.
After Jessica flew out, we investigated the church where the tragedy occurred.
Then we found a letter on the table left by the witch.
In the letter, Beatrice declares she is taking everything that gave to Grandfather back with an interest.
The interest was everything that Grandfather had given birth to.
This means that all of Grandfather's grandchildren, including me, are included in the interest!
But if someone solves the epitaph and discovers the hidden gold,
Beatrice shall renounce all rights to its recovery for all time. That is the special clause.
In addition, next to the letter, there are three gold bars inscribed with the crest of the One-winged Eagle. These prove that Grandfather's gold legend is real.
So this is the witch's letter of provocation.
This magic circle is...
This is the seventh magic circle of the sun.
The Hebrew words written around the circumference says
"The lord has freed me from my chains, I will offer to you the sacrifice of thanksgiving, and will call on the name of the Lord."
Killing Father and the rest was so that they could be sacrifices for this magic circle...?!
HAPPY HALLOWEEN FOR... MARIA
Oh, I see.
So is that why the key of this place was handed to Maria?
But why specifically choose the chapel?
Aunt Rosa, is there any special meaning to this chapel?
Special meaning?
We can't tell whether she called the six of them over here before killing them, or whether she killed them before carrying them over here.
But either way, it would take a lot of effort and risk.
Indeed. In doing something that elaborate, there would be an extremely high chance that when the police came, some disadvantage evidence would be found.
Then, there should be another meaning here.
Father wasn't a devout believer.
I don't know why, but he regards this place as sacred.
Ah, a long time ago he said that someday, he too might be able to receive a blessing there.
But unless a miracle occurred, that day would never come.
Miracle?
I don't know what it means, but it seems like to Grandfather that a fate that had been decided ever since he built this chapel.
Hey!
Look over there.
What does that mean?
M, B, T, Q... That is an incredible probability.
It's true that it can't be done without a miracle.
This means that the door will only open in case of a miracle.
You will be blessed only when a miracle occurs.
So it's a chapel that won't open?
Eh? Eh? Why?
Excuse me, what's wrong?
The key to this chapel...
Didn't Genji-san say there was only one key?
Yes, there is only one key that is usually kept in the key box in the servants' room.
Then someone stole it and put it in an envelope and handed it to Maria, just yesterday.
Huh? Well, isn't that strange?
What the hell is going on?
Before I took the key out of Maria's envelope and opened this door,
it was definitely locked.
But this key was in the envelope and in Maria's care, right?!
And it was before noon yesterday.
How did the culprit open the door?
How did they lock the door?
Another annoying closed room again?
Tell me, if it was a human, what trick could they have used to defeat it?
It's just like the closed rooms last time. Not enough information! It's impossible to reason like this!
Then let's do this, I shall add a new rule.
Rule?
From now on,
When I speak the truth, I will use red.
What do you mean?
You always keep running away by repeating "lack of information" and "uncertain basis".
Therefore, I want to give you the information and basis you want.
From now on.
Everything I speak in red is the truth!
There's absolutely no need to doubt it!
Are you telling me to believe that?
In a game, the rules are sacred! Those who take that lightly are not qualified to play!
Fine, I'll accept that rule.
Continue where we left off.
Dad and the rest used a hidden door to enter the chapel, or were carried in through it
Regardless of whether they were alive or dead, the six definitely enter through the door.
Do you have any proof?
Stop! I will supplement the rule.
When I speak the truth, I will use red.
However, I do not bear the responsibility of establishing that by showing proof
Anything said in red is simply the truth
The reason is simple. I carried out all of the crimes with magic. That makes anything possible.
What an unfair game.
So shall we resume once more? How will you defeat this closed room?
The culprit secretly made a duplicate key.
Only one key to the chapel exists!
The culprit made something other than a legitimate key and opened the door!
It is impossible to unlock the lock to the chapel without the chapel's key!
There's some kind of trick with the door. Even while it is locked, there was some way to pass through it
Is this the intelligence of humans, Battler?
When the door to the chapel is locked, it prevents any and all methods of entry or exit!
Damn it, damn it.
Think, don't give up! How can I not get checkmated by the witch?
Checkmate...?
When considering something, the closer you get to the very, very end, the easier it becomes to anticipate.
So when the opponent has only one move left,
Flip the chessboard around!
The only way to get into the chapel is through that door, and there's only one key.
But the important thing is whether that key was really in Maria's possession since noon yesterday.
Although Maria got the envelope from you yesterday,
if the key in the envelope is a fake...
Ridiculous.
This morning, Rosa definitely took an envelope of Maria's handbag,
and from that obtained the genuine key to the chapel.
I will keep going.
"Until Aunt Rosa took out the envelope, that envelope was completely under Maria's supervision."
Turn of the Golden Witch! Show me how you defeat that.
I refuse.
"Until Aunt Rosa took out the envelope, no one was able to touch Maria's handbag."
I refuse this, and I won't explain why.
Then let me explain for you.
Yesterday, you entrusted Maria with the key, some time between then and this morning
The culprit stole the envelope from Maria's handbag. They locked the chapel with the key.
And put the key back in the envelope sealed it with wax once more, and returned it to Maria's handbag.
There's no need for magic! This is a closed room trick possible for humans!
I give up! I resign! Just once, on this one board, I will give up!
But, you really are naive.
Just tell me.
Do you still not understand? As long as you continue to deny my existence, you will eventually be forced to suspect those relatives.
You will certainly accept my existence!
I wonder if the culprit is still on this island.
It's really unsettling.
I think so too.
Setting aside whether the culprit is that mysterious guest of honor or not, it's still very unpleasant.
That's right, we've been suspecting that vistor who called herself Beatrice.
There's the possiblity that she's a victim whose body still hasn't been found.
Beatrice-sama was not in her room.
Where's Jessica?
Jessica is currently being looked after by Kanon-san.
We should probably meet up with them soon.
The culprit is telling us to solve the riddle of the epitaph, I wonder if they are planning to snatch away the gold.
Beatrice hasn't said a thing about wanting gold.
Beatrice is just asking whether everyone can solve the riddle of the epitaph or not.
Cut it out, Maria.
Aunt Rosa... what is that?
This belong to Father. I borrowed it specially.
Is Grandfather okay?
He's fine. He said that he won't leave his room, so he's probably safe.
Now, we should do all we can to gather in the same place.
Yes, I also think that is good!
Oh! Maybe it would be good to call Milady here.
Then, I'll go with a couple people!
No!
Let's all go together. This is a "wolves and sheep puzzle".
Eh?
Genji, you lead the way.
Yes.
We all move together to keep the sheep from being attacked by wolves.
If there is a wolf in sheep clothing among us...
No... There's no way...
Stop!
What's this?
Another magic circle?
It's the first magic circle of the moon. It has the power to open the closed door.
Milady!
Milady, are you there?
The door is locked...
We have no choice. Open it with the master key.
Jessica-sama!
Jessica!!
How could Jessica even?!
Hey, Jessica!
This is... horrible. Not much time has passed since she died.
Where is Kanon-kun?!
Everyone, be quiet!
Find out if there is anyone hiding in the room.
And what is this key? If anyone knows, tell me.
It is probably the key to Milady's room.
The only key that can open this door is this one and the servants' master keys.
Correct.
How many master keys are there?
We servants each hold one master key. There are no additional ones.
Wait a second... In the last game, I thought we said there were extra master keys?
Having several master keys whose locations are unknown is quite troublesome.
So, I have altered the setup.
The only master keys are the ones held by the servants, one key each.
Messing with me like this...
More importantly, what is your next move?
You will see, if you listen to Rosa.
Thank you. I've sorted out the situation.
Aunt Rosa.
Basically, Jessica-chan's key is here. That means it was impossible for this room to be locked with anything but the master keys.
You don't mean you are suspecting us, the servants?
That's too harsh!
It's just a simple process of elimination.
So, that would make the most suspicious person the one who's missing right now.
Surely you don't mean Kanon-kun?!
Even if Beatrice is the culprit, there is also the possiblity that he is an accomplice!
How could you say that?!
Don't be careless, even if Kanon shows up safely.
...Unless he can be proven innocent.
Assume that the culprit who killed Jessica-chan is Kanon-kun.
What is this? Why are they treating Kanon-kun like the culprit, just because there's no corpse?
It doesn't matter, because I was finally able to be of use to Milady.
I hate this. Someone...
Please defend Kanon-kun's honor!
It's useless...
It's all useless.
Battler-sama.
Did you find evidence that Kanon-kun isn't the culprit?
Then Battler-kun, which of the other servants do you suspect?
Not just the servants. No one in our family is going to kill because of a pile of money!
Then, how are you going to prove that Kanon is not the culprit?
It's pretty simple.
Kanon-kun was not holding a master key.
Huh?
Gohda-san. You and Kanon chased after Jessica to the VIP room, right?
Yes?
Yes.
Whose key was used to unlock the VIP room at that time?
It was Kanon-san's.
Ahh!
I see. Then, if Jessica-chan didn't give that key back to Kanon-kun...
Doctor Nanjo, would you mind checking for us?
Here it is.
There's no doubt, this is the master key.
In other words, Kanon-kun could not have locked this room.
It does seem that way.
But, as long as we cannot find Kanon-kun. That doesn't change the fact that he is suspicious.
Just stop this, Aunt Rosa.
Eh?
It can be a little hard to keep people from suspecting each other in this situation.
But...
I will not permit accusations without evidence.
If you're going to accuse someone of being guilty, prepare some perfect evidence!
Well done, well done. Not a bad job.
You splendidly proved that Kanon could not have locked this door.
Then, who locked the door?
Shut up. Let's keep going.
First, I would like to verify what you mean by "this room is a closed room."
Very well.
There are absolutely no types of hidden doors. This door is the only way in or out.
The only way to lock this door is with Jessica's single key or the master keys, only one of which is held by each servant.
Repetition requested. "Kanon-kun was killed in this room".
Mmhm.
Kanon was killed in this room.
Again, repetition requested.
"Kanon-kun's corpse is in this room."
I refuse. I can't repeat it. Because I erased the corpse with magic.
Repetition requested. "The last time it was locked was with a master key".
I also refuse that.
This refusing thing is really vague.
Back when discussing the lock to the chapel, you completely turned the tables on me.
Ah, speaking of the chapel, it's the same here as well.
When locked, entry is not possible by any means.
Moreover,
No trick could have the effect of locking the door from the outside without using a key.
You should stop using the red when I don't ask for it.
Let's back up!
My purpose is to figure out how these crimes were committed by the 19th person, the human visitor,
so I don't have to suspect anyone.
What a foolish man.
This room wasn't originally a closed room.
After all, there are six keys that can open the lock.
There are also several people with these keys, so you can suspect them as much as you'd like.
That's...
But you deliberately denied all of this and created a closed room of your own.
Do you understand?
This is a closed room made from the contradictions in your own thinking.
Damn. As long as I suspect relatives, everything's fine?
No way!
But, I definitely can't accept the existence of a witch!
The only answer I can give now is...
...I resign.
Huh? What did you just say?
I give up. I was able to prove that Kanon-kun couldn't have locked this door.
But, I couldn't figure out who killed Jessica.
But Battler-sama, for Kanon-kun's sake—
And that also means being suspicious of other people.
Battler-kun...
Aunt Rosa, sorry. It's not like I wanted to resist you.
It's alright. I was also a little rash. Let's make up.
We are mutually-dependent sheep, but because I deny the witch...
It means acknowledging there are wolves among us at the same time.
What the hell am I supposed to do?
Shannon, be careful.
Okay, I'll be right back from the servants' room as soon as I have the essentials ready for tonight.
I'm sorry to have asked Doctor Nanjo to leave as well.
I would like to discuss something amongst the relatives.
No, it's okay.
Then, we will take our leave.
Aunt Rosa, can I go with them?
No.
Now, everyone here is a member of the Ushiromiya family.
Do you mean to say that you have chased out all the "wolves"?
Battler-kun, you are a quick thinker.
Wolves?
Aunt Rosa has decided that the servants are wolves of the "wolves and sheep puzzle,"
which means treating them like accomplices.
How could it be that simple?
Regardless of whether Beatrice is the real culprit or not.
I think there are multiple conspirators.
The first murder where Nii-san and the rest were killed — do you think a single person could have pulled that off?
But... if the servants were the culprits, why would they lock the door after killing Jessica?
In doing so, it'd be inevitable that they'd be suspected since they hold the master keys.
If you can lock the door to that room without the master key, that's another matter.
But that's not possible.
The whole uproar in Jessica's room about Kanon-kun being the culprit was to test the reactions of the servants?
That's right, it made me even more suspicious of them.
There's definitely a wolf among the servants.
Then isn't Shannon in danger right?
Shannon-chan went with Genji-san to see Father earlier.
She was supposedly isolated then, but she wasn't killed.
Because Genji-san isn't a wolf either, right?
Wrong. It's because they're both wolves.
Shannon isn't that kind of person who would take part in such a wicked crime! Please take back what you just said!
Even I don't think I deserve any praise right now!
But, I'm a mother! Maria's mother. And now, to both of you. So, I cannot let my guard down!
Always stay where I can see you.
I... will protect you.
While you're at it, you'll be observing us to make sure we are not wolves.
What about you, Aunt Rosa? Can you prove you're not a "wolf"?
Of course I can.
With this.
Just think about it, if I were the culprit!
Now that the servants are gone, would I miss this once-in-a-lifetime opportunity?
That is a crude theory, but it does make sense.
I'm sorry, but you have to understand that I'm trying to protect you from this malicious culprit.
For that purpose, I'd become a demon.
That is all it is.
Speaking of which, is the Master okay?
He's safe in his study.
There is a fully equipped refrigerator.
What happens to us now?
Is it Rosa-sama?
Genji-san.
Hm...
Dr. Nanjo and the women, stand back.
Kanon-kun? Kanon-kun!
Are you alright?
We must inform Rosa-sama.
Wait!
Don't... tell Rosa-sama.
Wh- what do you mean, Kanon-kun!
Rosa-sama came...
...to Milady...
...and I...
What did you say?
Curse you, Rosa...
I'm going to kill you... I'm going to kill you!
Shannon-san!
If Rosa-sama is the culprit,
what will happen to Battler-sama and the others?!
But, wouldn't it be better if we didn't provoke them too much...?
She said she'll massacre us all.
In order to have the Master's wealth all to herself, she told me clearly.
K- Kanon, are you okay?
Oh, this? It isn't a serious wound.
Watch.
Kanon-san, stop it!!
It is, not a serious wound.
Nee-san. Where'd you go?
I went to look for something.
More importantly, answer me.
Are you really... Kanon-kun?
What do you have in your hand?
This is a handkerchief with a spider's web stucked onto it.
If you're Kanon-kun, then you should be fine.
But if the spider is your natural enemy,
Kumasawa-san!
You senile old furniture!
Gohda!
Genji-sama!
You bastard!
Let... Let go of me!
Don't let that thing near me!
Aahhhhhhhh!
Gohda, you're not hurt, are you?
What... did we see?
I don't understand!
Shannon-chan and the others told us what they saw
But I couldn't believe that it was the truth.
It's like a B-rated horror movie.
But they said it did happen, that they saw it.
We went to the servant room together dubiously.
And then, after unlocking the door again,
It can't be!
What's wrong?!
The two bodies... aren't here!
Same as Jessica's room? They've disappeared from inside a closed room again?!
Please believe us, Rosa-sama! We definitely...
Be quiet!
This is a message from the person who hid the body.
It's the same as the one from the chapel.
People of the Ushiromiya family.
I wonder if your attempts at solving the epitaph have gotten far.
Solving the epitaph is the single method by which you can stop me.
You will not be able to stop me, or this ritual, by way or any other method of any kind.
I ask you all to not mistake your goal.
Attempting to search for me is useless.
Attempting to escape from me is useless.
Attempting to deny me is useless.
Beatrice the Golden.
Damn.
P.S: The remains of the two have been borrowed for the ritual.
I'll return them later, so please forgive me.
Furthermore, since these keys belong to all of you, I'm returning them.
These are Kanon's and Kumasawa's master keys.
Come on, damn it...
So we can only suspect the servants holding keys again?
I won't say it in red, alright?
By the way, what about the original keys to the servant room?!
Those are kept in the key box in center of the servant room.
Other than that, the conditions have not changed.
Entry or exit is impossible except for the single door and single window.
And those were both locked.
The door and the windows do not permit any kind of entry or exit when they are locked.
Of course,
It is impossible to unlock the door without a key to the servant room or the master key.
It's useless, it's all useless.
Think. Think!
Flip the chessboard around.
Carry the corpses, leave the letter, and lock the door, without relying on a hidden door.
Escape?
I got it.
Beato, before my repetition request.
I want to first check the definition of what you mean by hidden doors.
What have you thought of?
A hidden door refers to an entrance or exit that cannot be recognized by those who do not know of it.
In other words, if it doesn't get to the outside of the room, it's not a hidden door.
Hoh... Here it comes
I kept thinking that it was something that let the culprit escape the closed room.
But, this was not the case.
Even the culprit couldn't escape the closed room!
In other words, if there were, for example, something like a "hidden shelf" or a "secret closet," they wouldn't be defined as "hidden doors."
The third person in Jessica's room was hiding here, waiting for us to leave.
And at this very moment,
The culprit is still hiding in the servant room!
Repetition requested! "There is no one in this room other than us."
By us, I mean me, George-aniki, Maria, Aunt Rosa, Genji-san, Gohda-san, and Shannon-chan.
If you refuse, then I will keep going.
Repeat this!
There is no one in this room other than your group.
"Your group" refers to Battler, George, Maria, Rosa, Genji, Gohda, and Shannon.
What?
Let's go back to Jessica's room.
When Jessica's corpse was discovered, in Jessica's room
only Battler, George, Maria, Rosa, Genji, Gohda, Shannon, Kumasawa, and Nanjo were there.
This also includes the corpse of Jessica.
Therefore, both in the case of Jessica's room and the case in this servants' room, no humans exist that you were not aware of. No one is hiding.
And I'll say more.
No method exists by which the door can be locked from the outside without using a key.
And there's no method that exists to lock a window from the outside.
And while I'm at it,
You are incompetent!
Hihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihi!!
The light... was swallowed up by the deep red sea...
Now it's clear. There's no more room for doubt.
Rosa-sama...
Those two that you kept saying were dead aren't here.
And now we have the letter from Beatrice, where she was kind enough to confess that she carried the corpses off.
I've had enough of this farce!
F- farce, you say, what do you mean?
Since we cannot find the corpses, there's no reason we should accept that those two were killed.
Please wait a moment, this is-
Doctor Nanjo and Kumasawa-san are still alive!
They made it seem like they were killed, and are hiding somewhere in this mansion.
Rosa-sama!!
All the servants of the Ushiromiya swear that nothing of the sort happened!
Shut up!
As long as I can't find their corpses, there is no way to deny the possibility that you are wolves!
You and you!
All of you were bought off by blinding gold!
Rosa-sama, even we...!
Be silent!
I can't believe that you would repay a ten-year long debt of gratitude with betrayal!
Aunt Rosa!
How could you... go that far?
How did it turn out like this?
Rosa-sama is acting in a state of emergency.
We are furniture that serves the Ushiromiya family...
...and this key was entrusted to me as a proof of trust.
If that has been lost, I think it is only natural that I return it.
...You two.
Maria, give me that handbag.
Uu — ...
You are holding all five of the keys. Are you satisfied now, Aunt Rosa?
Yes, of course I'm satisfied.
Even if I can't trust anyone, I can at least trust myself!
Now... I don't have to suspect anyone anymore!
Beatrice can open doors with magic.
It doesn't matter who carries the keys!
Didn't I always tell you to stop laughing like that?!
What, Battler-kun?
Please, stop already...
Maria was right.
What are you talking about?
Maria...
...I'm sorry for doubting you.
It's all because I don't believe in witches.
That is why,
I am in so much pain...
...and this sad.
Battler-san...
I don't want to suspect anyone anymore!
That's fine, Battler!
Beatrice 'exists', and because Battler believed in Beato, he will surely be invited to the Golden Land.
Let's solve the riddle of the epitaph together with Maria.
Beato has been saying it from the beginning, that she wants to play and solve the epitaph.
Right.
Ah... that's right.
We...
...should have just believed from the start.
Although we have returned the master keys, our loyalty will not change
You truly are an admirable man.
When the typhoon passes, if the cries of the seagulls return to this island again...
...we will be able to trust each other again.
Then it will be my greatest joy.
I'm... going with them, too.
Aniki!
Battler-kun, stay with Aunt Rosa in the parlor.
I... want to stay by her side.
Uu —! Maria will protect Battler.
Well, good luck Maria-chan!
Then with that, we will be off. If you will excuse us.
You can't trust them at all,
damn furniture.
...What?
There are only five master keys? They must still be hiding more.
As if we could trust them just because they pulled keys out of their pockets.
You can't do this.
They ended up doing this for us!
This is a Devil's proof!
You can show that there are five master keys by glancing at them.
But, you can't prove that no more than five exist!
Only a demon or a witch could prove something like that!
Stop this, please, Beatrice.
Show yourself right now and tell them that there's no more than five keys, and there's no need to suspect anyone!
There are only five master keys. There are only five master keys.
What's going on? No matter what I say, it won't reach Rosa's ears.
It seems that some people still exist that deny me, so she can't hear it.
I accept it, you exist, you exist, you definitely exist!
Then show me with your actions!
Take off your clothes and become completely naked,
and use your tongue to lick my shoes.
When you do, I'll appear and say it in red!
Ushiromiya Battleeeeeeeer!
This is all my fault.
It was all because I broke the mirror, that it became the power to revive Beatrice-sama
Shannon, you don't have to bring that up.
But if it's true,
Can we seal Beatrice-sama with a mirror?
Ordinary mirrors probably won't...
I have heard that Madam keeps a spirit mirror as a charm.
Aunt Natsuhi?
I heard that it is a mirror that held a very strong magic repelling power, of high pedigree?
I've heard Aunt Natsuhi came from a family of Shinto priests.
Maybe we can really resist Beatrice.
I have heard Madam say that she keeps it safe in a treasure box.
Let's go. There's nothing else we can do.
It is worth a try.
But the door to Madam's room is locked.
In that case, Aunt Natsuhi should have been walking around with that key.
You can break the windows of the chapel and get in.
I'm sorry I can't go with you.
Huh?
So that the Master can call for me at any time, I must remain here.
This is the duty of the Ushiromiya family's servant.
I see.
Please take care.
Like the letter suggested, Maria and I started to challenge the riddle of the epitaph.
On the first twilight, sacrifice the six chosen by the key.
On the second twilight, those who remain shall tear apart the two who are close.
Obviously this hinted at the murders that have already taken place.
Then... On the fourth twilight, gouge the head and kill.
On the fifth twilight, gouge the chest and kill.
On the sixth twilight, gouge the stomach and kill.
On the seventh twilight, gouge the knee and kill.
On the eighth twilight, gouge the leg and kill.
If we assume that Doctor Nanjo and Kumasawa were both sacrifices
There should be three more.
Uu —. Baa-ttaa-leeeer!
What was it again, that Beatrice said she would do if we solve this riddle?
If the epitaph is solved, the ceremony is over, and no one else is going to die.
Committing these serial murders,
and deliberately telling us the conditions for her own defeat?
It's almost like she doesn't care whether she wins or loses.
What exactly is your goal?
It is painful no matter how many times I see it.
Madam, please excuse me.
I found it, the key to Madam's room.
Shannon-san!
What a wonderful reception for the host of the mansion.
These are the exact three people I was looking for.
I found it, but this box is locked.
Pry it open quickly, George-sama.
Shannon-san!
Who is it? Stop it!
Hey, can you see that? Your life flashing before your eyes.
Gohda.
The roulette has chosen you and George.
Shannon, you wanted to be embraced by your beloved, right?
You want him to teach you a woman's pleasure, right?
Your regret is hanging from your mouth. I can see it dribbling from corner of your lips.
I found it.
One step too late.
Sh-shannon.
George stay there. Don't move. I don't want to shift the central axis.
Excellent power, furniture!
I'm not furniture and right now I think you're very pitiful.
What?
George-san and I have sworn our love to each other, our eternal vows were completed!
So I have no regrets.
Enough! Stop talking you damn furniture, you trash scrap of furniture!
I am sorry!
I still can't do it.
Thank you for fighting for me.
That alone makes me happy.
George-san, in the end...
Please let me hear you say "I love you."
Yes, Sayo.
I will always...
Who is it?
It's me, Genji.
Say it right there.
The bodies of Doctor Nanjo and Kumasawa were found in the backyard.
On the seventh twilight, gouge the knee and kill.
On the eighth twilight, gouge the leg and kill.
Just as you described, they both have wounds on their necks.
But, what is this, a stake?
I do not know.
Knees and leg, this is the seventh and eighth twilight of the sacrifice.
Wait, that means...!
Doctor Nanjo and them were killed in this manner.
In other words, it is already,
On the fifth twilight, gouge the chest and kill.
On the sixth twilight, gouge the stomach and kill.
And then...
Use this.
Aniki!
How!
Chest and... stomach...
and...
On the fourth twilight, gouge the head and kill.
Battler-kun, you mustn't touch anything until the police arrive!
Maria!
What was the ninth twilight again?
On the ninth twilight, the witch shall revive, and none shall be left alive.
I see.
Are we going to die after this?
On the tenth twilight, the journey shall end, you will arrive at the Golden Land.
The witch shall praise the wise and bestow four treasures.
One shall be all the gold from the Golden Land.
One shall be the resurrection of all the dead souls.
One shall be the resurrection of the love that was lost.
One shall be to put the witch to sleep for all time.
After all of this, you're still leaving Genji to be alone?
When did this..?
Have you made more progress with the epitaph?
Time is quickly running out
The ninth twilight is about to begin
Battler, what is that?
I don't know when it got here.
Maria, come here.
Battler-kun.
I have concluded that you are a "wolf".
Why?!
When I entered this room, that letter wasn't there.
Only you could have put the letter there.
You're suspecting me because of that? My dad and family were all killed.
You have a point.
Even if you could have received a large sum of money,
Who would sell their own flesh and blood parents for this reason?
Unless you're not the real Ushiromiya Battler.
Huh? What's with this ridiculous thinking!
I haven't seen you for six years.
In other words, you could be a stranger who's trying to swindle the Ushiromiya family's fortune!
Is that so?
Then
I should be suspecting you!
What are you saying!
You should be proving it to me!
If I were a wolf, I would have shot you with this gun.
That's not a reason.
Speaking of relatives, six of them died. Why are you the only one alive?
There's only one reason
Because you killed Dad and them.
The witch did it, it is neither of your fault, it's nobody's fault.
That's right
It's all the witch's doing.
This was all a crime Beatrice committed with magic.
Please, hurry up and show yourself.
And confess to us that everything was your doing.
Hey, you won!
You do exist!
Show yourself!
Beatrice!
Beatrice, if I can see your smiling face one more time, I don't need anything else
Please, let me say a word of apology.
Kinzo, you fool.
Why can't you just say something simpler?
I love you, Beatrice.
Who is it?
Could it be?
Hey, hey! The door's not locked at all.
Pardon me.
Are you here to carry out my last rites?
The ceremony has been completed by the eighth twilight.
I believe it should be alright to tell you everything now.
Ah?
I shall guide you to the master's study.
From here on, Battler-sama you will probably see things that are incomprehensible.
Believe it or not, it's up to you.
Yeah, I'm ready.
How can I counter this? I've thought for 30 years.
This is fun, so much fun!
What the hell is this？
You made it, Ushiromiya Battler.
Since you called my name many times, I came to allow you to ask me anything.
There are a ton of things I want to ask!
What exactly is going on on this island and why is this happening?
And about the closed rooms!
What happened in the chapel?
What about Jessica's room?
What about Aunt Natsuhi's room?
What about the servant's room?
What about the parlor?!
What is your goal?
What do you want us to do?
Why did you call me here?!
Very well. However, I have one condition.
...What is it?
After listening to everything, if you are able to accept my existence,
Kneel down and kiss my shoes.
I called you here to make you surrender.
Yeah, sure! I'll kiss you or do whatever else for you!
Very good, let's start with what a witch is!
And so the witch began to tell of everything.
She started providing answers to all of Battler's questions.
Everything was logical.
Everything made sense.
So Battler had no choice but to admit it.
The witch truly did "exist".
All that's left is a tale that doesn't need to be told.
After toppling the king and resigning, all that remains is to reflect on one's moves.
And set the pieces up once more.
The winner is the Golden Witch, Beatrice.
When the seagulls cried,
none were left alive.
Show yourself! I know you're there, Beatrice!
Even if it's just this one piece...
The door to the Golden Land is about to open.
Stop laughing like that.
Where are you, show yourself, Beatrice!
What? What is this?
Mama!
Silence!
Tonight marks the revival of our Golden Witch.
Beatrice will now make her entrance.
Thank you for gathering tonight for the me!
It is time for me to open the gate of the Golden Land.
Beatrice, now is the time to send me to the Golden Land!
Drink, eat, sing, dance, laugh, intimidate, assault, return.
Get down on your knees to pay your respects.
Swear to give all flesh and blood to me.
You're not even worthy to be my furniture.
Is entertaining the guests the most you can do now?
Maria, quickly, quickly!
Mama, wait for me.
Maria!
Mama!!
Try laying one finger on Maria, I dare you.
I'll show you just how lukewarm the hell you came from is!
Mama!
Load the bullets in, quickly!
Uu —!
I'll show you... what my golden dream looks like!
Mama, the bullets are loaded.
Good job! Stay next to me!
Mama, are you alright?
Mhm!
Mama!
Just what has my life been anyway?
I lost all my money,
was looked down on by my siblings,
I even put Maria in danger.
Mama, Mama!
Maria...
Mama just remembered something she needs to do.
Go ahead without me!
No, no no no no no!
I want to stay with you, I don't want Mama to die!
You'll say you want to stay with me, even though I am such a bad Mama?
I want to stay with Mama, I want to stay with you.
I always make it look like I put you first, but I always put you off.
Even though I am such a bad Mama?!
You know, there's only one Mama in the whole world.
So I'll be happy as long as the one Mama in the world is with me.
I was such an idiot...
I didn't need any gold! I should have just held your hand!
Maria, we'll always be together.
Uu —!
Whoever wants to eat the bullets Maria chambered for me...
Step forward!
Eh? What am I doing?
My body feels heavy...
My head feels dizzy.
I can grant you whatever it is that you desire. Think of it as a reward for your good luck.
Eh?
Who?
I am the Golden Witch. I would have no problem bestowing you a mountain of gold.
But, it seems that this wouldn't satisfy you.
Rosa!
Why are you so stupid?
Stop it...
Idiots shouldn't interrupt, Rosa.
Stop it!
It can't be helped, right? After all, it's Rosa.
I hate my brothers and sisters!
I see, your pain is a fate you have shouldered from the time you were born.
Then I shall give you the joy of having your days of suffering rewarded.
Food accounts for much of a human's pleasures.
Why don't we hold a gourmet banquet that will continue until the pain in your heart is healed?
Eh?
The apéritif is a cocktail. If I had to give it a name, it'd be called a Bloody-Krauss.
Isn't it delicious? It's been dyed with golden drops of blood squeezed out of your brother, Krauss, after placing him in a compressor.
No, stop!
Next...
Forked-tongued salad made from seasonal vegetables.
It's made with Eva's tongue, which you always wished you could bite off one day.
And that's not all...
Next is a sea bass pie wrapped in the skin of Rudolf's face.
No, no...
NOOOO!!
You're thrilled, aren't you, Ushiromiya Rosa? Don't pretend like you don't like it!
No, stop...
I planned to keep the dessert a secret to surprise you,
but I suppose I'll reveal it. Perhaps revealing it now will give you the incentive to finish the main course.
It's oven-baked Maria and apples. Eat that, and you will be freed from everything.
No, don't do it!!
Mama, was Maria a burden?
You're not a burden, not a burden!
Whenever Mama went to stay over with a man, I would get lonely and make a mess of my room.
When I go to search for Mama by myself, I get lost...
Because I'm like this... I'm a burden to Mama.
I'm sorry for being born!
Maria!
So, I'll become delicious oven-baked apples for Mama's sake.
In that case, will mom feel really good for the first time?
Maybe if you eat me, you'll think I am delicious!
I don't want that!
Mama, thanks for everything.
Wait, Maria, I don't want this! No!!
Then I will have you acknowledge it.
Acknowledge the fact that I'm a witch.
I acknowledge it... I acknowledge that Beatrice is a witch.
So give Maria back to me!!
I finally got you to acknowledge it! Perfect.
It's perfect!
Now, take Maria away! Prepare a delicious oven roast for Rosa.
NOOOO!!
Looks delicious!
How about you slice up those cow tits of yours and make me a sandwich?
Battler?! You bastard... You should have already surrendered down to your very soul!
Me too, but while I was listening to that gross recipe, I started to get a little hungry.
I started craving a whole roast witch!
What?
Also, Maria.
It's ten years too early for you to talk about having someone eat you up. But in ten years, you'd better say that to me.
Promise?
Uu, I promise.
Battler-kun...
Sorry to keep you waiting, Aunt Rosa.
This is a one-on-one fight between me and this woman.
I absolutely...
...cannot surrender!
How amusing! I wouldn't have you any other way, Ushiromiya Battler!
In that case, just try to deny me!
I will make you surrender over and over again!
Ah... it's useless.
It's
It's all
It's all useless!